# **Héctor Olivares Navarro**

# Web Developer

📞 +52 55 1074 6206 🛮 hectorolivares033@gmail.com 🔀 hectorolivares.me 🕡 github.com/hectorolivares

#### **About me**

I am a web developer with experience in TypeScript, React, and Tailwind CSS, currently studying Computer Engineering at UNAM. I am passionate about programming and always strive to stay up-todate with the latest trends and technologies to improve my skills as a developer. I consider myself a very committed worker and enjoy collaborating with others to achieve common goals.

My goal as a web developer is to create innovative and efficient solutions to the problems that arise in software development. I see myself as a creative, analytical, and problem-solving person.

# **Skills**

# **Programming languages**

TypeScript, JavaScript(ES6), HTML, CSS/Scss/Sass, Python

# Frameworks/Libraries/Others

React, Vue, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Node.js, Webpack, WordPress, Netlify, Vercel, NPM, Git, Command line

# **UX/UI Design**

Responsive Design, Prototyping, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator

# **Currently learning**

Next.js, SQL, Java

# Education

# Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México (National Autonomous **University of Mexico)**

B.E. in Computer Engineering, with specialization in Software Engineering

August 2020 - Present

# **Projects**

# Bazar Yokai

eCommerce project focused on the reuse and relocation of objects. It offers a wide range of products at affordable prices, promoting a sustainable and responsible lifestyle. The project's mission is to promote the circular economy and contribute to the care of the environment.

# **Experience**

# Freelance Web Developer

Design and development of websites that help to advertise projects and/or businesses of the people who work with me.

July 2022 - Present

# Languages

English (Intermediate) Spanish (Native)

# **Interests**

App development, game development, digital content creation, running, football, sports, reading, movies, philosophy and architecture.

# **Héctor Olivares Navarro**

# Desarrollador web

\$\omega\$ +52 55 1074 6206
\omega\$ hectorolivares033@gmail.com
\$\omega\$ hectorolivares.me

o github.com/hectorolivares

# Sobre mí

Soy un desarrollador web con experiencia en TypeScript, React y Tailwind CSS, actualmente estudiando Ingeniería en Computación en la UNAM. Me apasiona la programación y siempre me esfuerzo por estar actualizado en las últimas tendencias y tecnologías para mejorar mis habilidades como desarrollador. Me considero una persona muy comprometida y disfruto colaborar con otros para alcanzar objetivos en común.

Mi objetivo como desarrollador web es crear soluciones innovadoras y eficientes para los problemas que surgen en el desarrollo de software. Me veo a mí mismo como una persona creativa, analítica y resolutiva.

# **Habilidades**

# Lenguajes de programación

TypeScript, JavaScript(ES6), HTML, CSS/Scss/Sass, Python

# Frameworks/Librerias/Otros

React, Vue, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Node.js, Webpack, WordPress, Netlify, Vercel, NPM, Git, Command line

# **UX/UI Design**

Responsive Design, Prototyping, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator

# Actualmente aprendiendo

Next.js, SQL, Java

# Educación

# Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México, Facultad de Ingeniería

Ingeniería en Computación, con especialización en Ingeniería de Software.

# **Proyectos**

#### Bazar Yokai

Proyecto de eCommerce enfocado en la reutilización y reubicación de objetos. Se ofrece una amplia gama de productos a precios accesibles, fomentando un estilo de vida sostenible y responsable. La misión del proyecto es promover la economía circular y contribuir al cuidado del medio ambiente.

# Experiencia

## **Desarrollador Web Freelance**

Diseño y desarrollo de páginas web, que ayudan a publicitar proyectos y/ o negocios de las personas que trabajan conmigo.

Julio 2022 - Presente

#### **Idiomas**

Inglés (Intermedio) Español (Nativo)

# **Intereses**

Desarrollo de juegos, desarollo de apps, creación de contenido digital, correr, fútbol, deportes, lectura, películas, filosofía y arquitectura.

Agosto 2020 - Presente